thesecretofdeliberatecreation.com 2016-03-11

# Website Privacy Policy

The last update to our Privacy Policy was posted on August 22, 2015.  This document governs the privacy policy of our Websites.  Any capitalized terms not defined herein will have the same meaning as where they are defined elsewhere on our Website.

### _Definitions_

"Non-Personal Information" (NPI) is information that is in no way personally identifiable and that is obtained automatically when you access our Website with a web browser.

"Personally Identifiable Information" (PII) is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained for us to provide you with a product or service.  PII may include information such as your name, address, phone number, credit card information, and other related information that you provide to us. 

### _Our Commitment to Your Privacy_

Our Privacy Policy tells you what PII we may collect from you, how we may share your PII, and how you can limit our sharing of your PII.

Little e, Inc. is committed to the security and privacy of all our customers.  We take your privacy seriously, and we will work with you to ensure that you have an enjoyable online experience.

Little e, Inc. and our affiliates respect your privacy and recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of your PII you share with us.

### _Links to Other Websites_

Our Website may contain links to other websites.  You understand that these websites are not under our control and are not subject to our Privacy Policy.  These websites will likely have their own privacy policies.  We have no responsibility for these websites and provide links to these websites solely for your convenience.

You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is solely at your own risk.  It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies of these websites to see how they treat your personal information.

Rubbertree Inc. expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Rubbertree Inc. page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through Rubbertree Inc. you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Rubbertree Inc. is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Rubbertree Inc. does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in our forum, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Rubbertree Inc. and this policy. 

### _Information We Collect_

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website.  As a visitor to our Website, you can browse our Website to find out more about us.  You are not required to provide us with any PII as a Visitor.

However, if you register as a Member to use our Website, you must provide PII in order for us to provide you with various features and/or functionality from our Website.   As a Member, we collect your PII in the following ways: 

_**At Purchase/Member Registration**_

When you purchase from us and register for membership, we collect your name and email address and phone number.

_**Online Forms**_

There may be online forms used in our Website.  The information you enter into these online forms may contain PII.

_**Premium Features**_

Our Website may offer premium features for which you must pay to use.  If we were to charge you for the use of these premium features, we would need to collect payment source information (i.e. credit card) to bill you for using such premium features.

### _Computer Information Collected_

When you use our Website, we automatically collect certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website.  Such information is typically considered NPI.  We may also collect any of the following:

**_Cookies_**

Our Website uses “Cookies” to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited.  A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser.  We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website.  Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies.  However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all.  We never place PII in Cookies.

_**Web Beacons**_

We may also use a technology called, web beacons, to collect general information about your use of our Website and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails.  Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Website.  We do not link NPI from Web Beacons to PII without your permission.

**_Automatic Information_**

We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device.  This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our website.  This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system.  We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website. 

**_Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy_**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following link:   
<http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads>

_**Google Analytics Privacy Policy**_

Our website uses “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of our site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit our site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to our site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics to improve our site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit our site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit our site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use. <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html>

You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by [disabling cookies](http://www.usa.gov/optout_instructions.shtml) on your browser. <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

### _How Information is Used_

We use PII that you provide for our internal purposes, such as offering our services to you, confirming and tracking your order, subscription or registration; analyzing statistics and demographics; and informing you of new products, services, and offers as provided by us and/or our affiliates.

Our affiliates may have products, services, or offers about which you may be interested in receiving information and they may use the PII we have for you to contact you.  If you don’t want to receive information from our affiliates, you can let us know so you’re no longer contacted by our affiliates about their products, services, or offers.

We may also combine information you give us online or through printed forms; publicly available information; and information we receive from other parties.  We use this combined information for your online experience and to let you know about new products, services, offers, and other promotion.

To give you the best possible service, we may use our affiliates to provide contracted services for our business, including, but not limited to processing credit cards, hosting our website, shipping products to you, or advertising.  In many cases, we will need to provide some if not all the PII you provide to use so our affiliates can perform these services.  Our affiliates are only authorized to use your PII as provided within this Privacy Policy.

There are times that we may have to disclose your PII to comply with state and federal laws; to assist law enforcement and governmental agencies in preventing or investigating fraud or other crimes, or in response to a court order.  In such instances, we will only provide the PII requested and your PII will only be used for legal purposes as opposed to marketing.

Finally, if we sold or transferred our business, we would transfer your PII to the purchaser as appropriate and might also retain a copy of your PII for any new business ventures we would start.

### _Changing Your Information_

You may change your PII at any time using facilities found on our Website.  If you need assistance with updating your PII or removing yourself from our mailing lists, just send us an email with your request or contact us using the Contact us information found on our Website.

### _Opting Out of Sharing Information_

You can always opt out of future unaffiliated third-party disclosures of your information.  Such opt-out will not affect disclosures otherwise permitted by law including but not limited to: (i) disclosures to affiliates, (ii) disclosures to third-party service providers who provide certain services for our business, such as credit card processing, computer system services, shipping, data management, or promotional services, (iii) disclosures to third parties as necessary to fulfill your requests, (iv) disclosures to governmental agencies or law enforcement departments or otherwise required to be made under applicable law, (v) previously completed disclosures to third parties, or (vi) disclosures to third parties in connection with subsequent contests or promotions you may choose to enter, or third-party offers you may choose to accept.

### _“Do Not Track” Settings_

Some web browsers have settings that enable you to request that our Website does not track your movement within our Website.  Our Website does not obey such settings when transmitted to and detected by our Website. Due to circumstances that are outside our control (i.e. internet transmission issues, web browser/web server incompatibilities, etc.), we may not always be able to detect and honor this setting.  However, this does not change our compliance in any other way with our Privacy Policy.

**Change and Turn off tracking features in your browser.** You can turn off tracking features and other security settings in your browser by visiting the following links:

  * For Internet Explorer visit: <http://goo.gl/0taI7I>
  * For Mozilla Firefox visit: <http://goo.gl/IKxt9l>
  * For Google Chrome visit: <http://goo.gl/NQIkqE>
  * For Safari visit: <http://goo.gl/7XCOzL>

**Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.** Google provides a free add-on to most major browsers that you can install to prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics. Visit the following link to download the free Google Opt-out Add-on Tool: <http://goo.gl/Ls82zv>

### _Protecting Your Child’s Privacy_

We follow the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).  Even though our Website is not designed for use by anyone under the age of 18 (child), we realize that a child may attempt to access our Website.  We do not knowingly collect PII from a child.  If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child is using our Website, please contact us.  We may ask for proof of identification before we remove any information to prevent malicious removal of account information.  If we discover on our own that a child is accessing our Website, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it, we will not use the information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties.  You acknowledge that we do not verify the age of our users nor do we have any liability to do so.  If you are a child, please seek the permission of a parent or guardian before accessing our Website. 

### _Our Email Policy (REVISED)_

We comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us or our affiliates. We will not sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission except in the sale or transfer of our business.

### _Our Security Policy_

We have taken steps to build our Website using sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of your PII.   When we collect your PII through our Website, we will encrypt your PII before it travels over the Internet using industry standards as establishing for conducting secure online transactions.  We also use industry standard technologies such as secure routers and fire walls to make sure that your PII is safe.  Unfortunately, we cannot fully guarantee secure data transmission over the Internet because of its nature.

Once we receive your PII, we have industry standard security measures in place to protect against the loss or misuse of your PII, though again, we cannot fully guarantee against such loss or misuse.  We strongly urge you to protect any password you may have for our Website and not share it with anyone.  You should always log out of our Website when you are done using it, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place. 

### _Use of Credit Cards_

You may have to provide a credit card to buy products and services from our Website.  We use third-party billing services and HAVE NO CONTROL over these services.  We use our commercially reasonable efforts to make sure that your credit card number is kept STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL by using only third-party billing services that use industry-standard encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorized use.  However, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your credit card number. 

### _Changes to Our Privacy Policy_

As necessary to address changes in laws or our business practices, we may modify our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, to address these changes.  We will typically notify users by some message on our Website home page that our Privacy Policy has changed.  We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy.  Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.  We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to make sure you still agree with it.

### _Questions about Our Privacy Policy_

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us using the Contact us information found on our Website.

Copyright © Orion Systems. All Rights Reserved. This document, or any portion of, may not be copied or duplicated in any way without the written permission of Orion Systems. [http://www.DisclaimerTemplate.com](http://www.disclaimertemplate.com/)
